clear-reports.com 2016-03-28

# Privacy - ClearReports

## About ClearReports

This is the Privacy Policy of ClearReports (CR), a software product and service owned and operated by Clear Reports Limited (CRL), Studio 6, 84 Canfield Gardens, London NW6 3EE. CRL takes its responsibilities on the confidentiality of your personal information very seriously. Our Privacy Policy is set out below. Please read this Policy with care; it describes how we will process your data. If you have any questions or comments, email [dataprotection@clear-reports.com](mailto:dataprotection@clear-reports.com).

## Where your data is held

Your personal data is held on secure servers operated by CRL and agencies contracted by us. We do not transfer your data outside CRL and we comply with the protection offered to you under the Data Protection Act 1998.

## Data Security

Personal data is collected and stored securely subject to stringent security measures and is protected against misuse. When we use external data processing services, we do so only under strict contractual terms to mirror the security policies that we have in place.

## The information we collect

As well as name and contact details, we ask you to supply information about the type of organisation you work for or to tell us if you are a consumer; that and any other information we gather about you will help us tailor the information we send you to your needs.

## What we do with your data and what we don't do

We shall process the data you supply to give you information and advice regarding your enquiry. If you have given your consent, we may communicate with you via e-mail, SMS, post or telephone about the activities of CRL. We will not share your data for marketing purposes outside CRL.

This website explains how to subscribe to CRL communications. If you want to update your personal data and preferences for communications from us please email us at [support@clear-reports.com](mailto:support@clear-reports.com).

## External links

The CR website contains links to websites operated by third parties under different privacy policies. Should you choose one of those links, you will be leaving the CR site and this Privacy Policy will no longer apply.

## Access to your information

You have the right to ask CRL for a copy of the personal information CRL hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to correct any inaccuracies in that information. If you would like access to your information, please contact [dataprotection@clear-reports.com](mailto:dataprotection@clear-reports.com).

## Cookie Policy

The CR website cookie policy can be found here and informs users what cookies are used on this site and how to manage them.

## Newsletters

Our e-newsletters will be used to inform you of news related to CR and CRL, including events. Our subscription lists will not be sold, rented or leased to any third-parties. We use code within our e-newsletter template to identify open rates and click through rates. This enables us to identify which individuals have opened the message or clicked on links within it and better tailor any follow-up communications. You can remove your name from the subscription lists at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link within the newsletter.

## Copyright

Copyright in all information, text and images featured on our site is owned by or licensed to CRL.

## Changes to this policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we shall post changes on this page so that you are always aware of how CRL uses your personal information.
